[{"answer": "I was stunned.", "docId": "130102pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "When you heard about that what went through your mind immediately, Speaker?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "You know, look, I have a lot of respect for Congress member King.", "docId": "130102pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "Are you satisfied with the assurances that Congressman King got?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "You know, I don't really know why it's happening so long.", "docId": "130102pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "So -- why do you think -- why is it happening like this right now, taking so long?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "You know, look, I'm a Democrat.", "docId": "130102pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "You want him to remain as speaker of the House?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "Yes, it has.", "docId": "130102pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "It's been, what, a little bit more than two months?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": ".", "docId": "130102pmt", "aSentId": 147, "question": "What would you tell your congressional leaders if they were watching you right now?", "qSentId": 146}, {"answer": "I'm hearing just what you heard, which is that she's recovering and it's on track to be a complete recovery.", "docId": "130102pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "What are you hearing about her condition?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "I think all plans are as they were.", "docId": "130102pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "Is that still her intention, do you think?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "Well, anybody who knows Hillary Clinton knows she would much rather have been at the Senate, at the -- on the appointed day at the appointed time answering questions, and she did take responsibility because she knows what her role is and she knows what she should do and she does it on a daily basis.", "docId": "130102pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "What was your opinion?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "I will always support what contribution it is that Hillary Clinton believes that she can make and that will be her decision when the time comes.", "docId": "130102pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "This illness that we all hope she recovers completely, makes a full and speedy recovery, are you going to be with her if she runs for president again in 2016?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "I don't think she knows what she wants to do.", "docId": "130102pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "You agree with me?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "Sure he should.", "docId": "130102pmt", "aSentId": 258, "question": "Should -- should he be commended for putting his people's needs really ahead of party politics, if you will?", "qSentId": 257}, {"answer": "It's become a hot political issue because even for folks who believe that the government is doing too many things that ought to be left to individuals and the private- sector when it comes to things like taking care of people who have been hit by a disaster, taking care of people in emergency situations, that's something that I think everybody ought to be able to agree on.", "docId": "130102pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "I'm not entirely sure.", "docId": "130102pmt", "aSentId": 294, "question": "Do you think that reassurance is justified?", "qSentId": 293}, {"answer": "Well, I wasn't -- I wasn't aware of the rumblings that this was going to happen, but you know, you have to look at Al Jazeera.", "docId": "130102pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "What did you think?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "Well, I -- this is an explosion of far left wing network financially.", "docId": "130102pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "What do you think about all this, Margaret?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "You would come to me first, Wolf.", "docId": "130102pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "Are we going to be hearing all these details now for weeks and weeks and months and months?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "Well, you know, this is going to be a major, major Twitter moment because Kim Kardashian is -- I mean, I don't know the numbers but she's one of the top people on Twitter.", "docId": "130102pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "Leigh, you have any final thoughts in this?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "You know, I got to go check.", "docId": "130102pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "Hey, Wolf, do you follow Kim Kardashian?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "I was pretty surprised.", "docId": "130102pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "How stunned were you?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "Well, you know, here's the thing that people don't realize.", "docId": "130102pmt", "aSentId": 447, "question": "So do you believe he did the right thing by resigning?", "qSentId": 446}, {"answer": "Well, you know, there's an old saying -- generals retire only when they go to bed at night.", "docId": "130102pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "Even if you're retired?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "Well, I think he -- you know, the CIA is kind of a weird place when it comes to moral stands, too.", "docId": "130102pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "Do you think the president should have accepted that resignation?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "Well, that's a very good question.", "docId": "130102pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "Will this have been worthwhile for the United States?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "It was -- it was very difficult to keep that a secret from them.", "docId": "130102pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "How did you keep it a secret?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "I was just so excited and overwhelmed to see him.", "docId": "130102pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "Miriam, how did you feel when you realized that that was your husband?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "The only thing I can even say is -- Natural Balanced Pet Foods and, you know, Army Public Affairs Office, they had done such a great job here.", "docId": "130102pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "What's your wish, Sergeant, for other military families right now who are away from their loved ones?", "qSentId": 508}]